[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone. <br /><br />Click \"Continue\" when you're ready to move on.","rt":43355,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":63580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</ sub>, yo u start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3","4+5=9 9-6=3","3"],"rt":50816,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":114397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":5915,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":120313,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":" 5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6018,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":126332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":2471,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":128804,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":190012,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":318817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1376,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":320196,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4543,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":324740,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1295,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":326036,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your  result.  If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2076,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":328112,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1288,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":329400,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3044,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":332444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":924,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":333368,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2016,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":335384,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1171,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":336556,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br / ><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2692,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":339248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":983,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":340231,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3060,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":343291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":344252,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2435,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":346687,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":964,"trial_type":"fe edback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":347652,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.2-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":12543,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":360197,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the thing that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +< sub>6</s ub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":30258,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":390456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":43558,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":434015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":3019,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":437035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remembe r, the i nverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":439575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1203,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":440778,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":3197,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":443975,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1199,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":445175,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3108,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":448283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":948,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":449231,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<s ub>6</su b>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2183,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":451414,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1028,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":452442,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.6-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":29228,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":481670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":" We have  one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because of this, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":145786,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":627458,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which ca n make e very other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5371,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":632833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":1311,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":634145,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1962,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":636108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is  a genera tor under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":4927,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":641035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":43213,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":684249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because  4 = 4, 2  = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":2573,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":686823,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2869,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":689694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":999,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":690693,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.9-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9 </sub>,  on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":19177,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":709871,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3176,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":713048,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":811,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":713860,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What i s 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3058,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":716919,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8088,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":725008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3079,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":728087,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4218,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":732305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2667,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":734973,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"4+1=5, 5 is less than 9 so we leave the answer at 5.","response_history":["4+1=5, 5 is less than 9 so we leave the answer at 5."],"rt":28227,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":763200,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"8+4=12, 12 is more than  9 so we  subtract 12-9=3","response_history":["8+4=12, 12 is more than 9 so we subtract 12-9=3"],"rt":30346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":793548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"It's 0 because you need 0 to make 9.","response_history":["It's 0 because you need 0 to make 9."],"rt":48731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":842279,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"It's 4 because you need to add 4 to 5 to make 9.","response_history":["It's 4 because you need to add 4 to 5 to make 9."],"rt":17783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":860063,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["It's 7 becau","7"],"rt":9211,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":869275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"It's 6 because you need to add 6 to 3 to get to 9.","response_history":["It's 6 because you need to add 6 to 3 to get to 9."],"rt":15783,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":885059,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because there is no way to  make 2,  5, 7 under 9.","response_history":["No, because there is no way to a","No, because there is no way to make 2, 5, 7, ","No, because there is no way to make 2, 5, 7,","No, because there is no way to make 2, 5, 7 under 9."],"rt":2714116,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":3599176,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 under 9.","response_history":["No, because yh","No, because y","No, because there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, 6","No, because there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, 5, 7, 8 under 9."],"rt":159731,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":3758912,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your ans wer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because there is no way to make 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, 8 under 9 with just 5.","response_history":["No ","No ","Nom","No, because 5","No, because there is no way to make 2, 3, 4, 5, 7, 8 under 9 with just 5."],"rt":315188,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":4074103,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 under 9 with just 6.","response_history":["No, because there is no way to male","No, because there is no way to mal","No, because there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8 under 9 with just 6."],"rt":58082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":4132190,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.11-0"},{"instructions":"Now  we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use \"+_n\", and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":37604,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":4169798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 is the inverse of 5 under +_6","response_history":["1 =","1 +_6 5","1 is+_6 5","1 is +_6 5","1 is th+_6 5","1 is the+_6 5","1 is the +_6 5","1 is the i+_6 5","1 is the in+_6 5","1 is the inv+_6 5","1 is the inver+_6 5","1 is the inverse+_6 5","1 is the inverse +_6 5","1 is the inverse o+_6 5","1 is the inverse of+_6 5","1 is the inverse of +_6 5","1 is the inverse of  5+_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 +_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 u+_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 un+_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 und+_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 under+_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 under +_6 5","1 is the inverse of 5 under +_6 ","1 is the inverse of 5 under +_6"],"rt":351645,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":4521444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because you need 4 added to 2 to make 6.","response_history":["2 is the inverse of 4 under the","2 is the inverse of 4 under th","2 is the inverse of 4 under t","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because it takes","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because it take","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because it tak","2 is the inverse of 4 under + _6 becau se it ta","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because it t","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because it ","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because it","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because i","2 is the inverse of 4 under +_6 because you need 4 added to 2 to make 6."],"rt":100166,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":4621614,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I honestly don't know the answer to this.","response_history":["I honestly don't know the answer to this."],"rt":27031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":4648647,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<su b>n</sub >.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":8691,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":4657341,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":9937,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":4667280,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must divide n.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":15268,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":4682549,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I'm not sure how to explain whether this is true or false.","response_history":["I'm not sure how to explain how this is correct","I'm not sure how to explain how this is correc","I'm not sure how to explain whether this is true or false."],"rt":63690,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":4746239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":65887,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":4812130,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is corret.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"I'm not sure what the answer is to this question.","response_history":["I hone","I hon","I ho","I h","I ","I'm not sure what the answer is to this question."],"rt":39432,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":4851564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":18705,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":4870269,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.13-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press \"Continue\" to continue.","rt":2301,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":4872571,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"34","response_history":["34"],"rt":1914,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":4874486,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2005,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":4876492,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"General algebra.","response_history":["General algebra."],"rt":12792,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":4889285,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":4896188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":6247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":4902435,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":4905277,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4398,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":4909676,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":1775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":4911452,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":1452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":4912904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["eg","e","English"],"rt":5067,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":4917972,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":6353,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":4924326,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to und erstand  it. I still did the best I could on the HIT.","response_history":["I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did my best","I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did the best I could and ","I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did the best I could and","I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did the best I could an","I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did the best I could a","I understood most of the ma th at th e beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did the best I could ","I understood most of the math at the beginning of the HIT, but toward the end it just didn't make sense to me as hard as I tried to understand it. I still did the best I could on the HIT."],"rt":61862,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":4986188,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"}]